<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Van and Josie</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2015-08-18T18:28:14-04:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to Where I Left Off  ೕ(˃̵ᴗ˂̵ ๑)]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Back-To-Where-I-Left-Off/" />
  <id>/Back-To-Where-I-Left-Off</id>
  <updated>2015-07-12T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2015-08-18T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;(۶ꈨຶꎁꈨຶ )۶ʸᵉᵃʰᵎ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time I was going through some self studying. Studying to become a programmer/developer. Then out of no where, I landed a job as Junior Internal Developer at a tech firm called Whirlwind Technologies. This kinda changed my life. I say kinda because I feel more of the external things changed as in income. With higher income I studied the art of investing and now have a good amount of money in companies I believe in. I try to save as much as I can but I do spend when I want to, for example my recent purchase of $60 worth of in game items on an app game I play. No shame, I live my life the way I want to and you should too! Heh heh. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Back to the matter is that with this new job, This hasn’t changed my quest to becoming a master programmer. Sure I haven’t been studying as much as I would like to due to me settling in my new reality. But now Im back to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NORMALLY with a job or like any other responsibilty it’s harder to focus on my studies. That’s why I quit my last job at Micro Center. I needed time to myself. But no worries with my current job. My technical director encourages everyone to be innovative and continue to learn and become better. I can not ask for a better environment. Im a JUNIOR developer. I don’t have that much responsibilty but to learn and get better! My heart is like racing while I type this! Or .. My coffee is just kicking in.. But the point is Im sooo grateful and excited for this. I advise everyone to go and find a job that doesn’t suppress your efforts to go towards your true goal in life. Better yet! Find a job that supports that goal. Mine is to have time to study and get better at programming. My responsibilty within the company is just that. 
I recently asked my team lead that I wanted to go to New York and attend a tech bootcamp for 3-4 months to get better. He encourages it and is even going to see if he could have the company help pay for my tuition. I would be working at the same time since I work from home anyways. So I would not skip a beat. So Im in bound for New York sometime in the next couple of months. 
My friends support me, my family supports me, SO MY JOB WILL SUPPORT ME.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to be a master programmer so bad.. sooo badd. So here I go.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Once more into the fray…&lt;br /&gt;
Into the last good fight I’ll ever know…&lt;br /&gt;
To live and die on this day…&lt;br /&gt;
To live and die on this day…”  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;― The Grey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Back-To-Where-I-Left-Off/&quot;&gt;Back to Where I Left Off  ೕ(˃̵ᴗ˂̵ ๑)&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Van Phan  Josephine Kim at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Van and Josie&lt;/a&gt; on August 18, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Anything Fast ʕ•̥͡•ʔ]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Learning-Anything-Fast/" />
  <id>/Learning-Anything-Fast</id>
  <updated>2015-07-12T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2015-06-21T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;ʕ´•ᴥ•`ʔσ”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be my personal guide to help me stay on track with&lt;br /&gt;
skills that I am currently learning.&lt;br /&gt;
(Kaufman, Josh. &lt;em&gt;The First 20 Hours.&lt;/em&gt; New York: Penguin Group, 2014. Print)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1. The project must be lovable.
2. Focus your energy on one skill at a time.
3. Define your target performance level.
4. Deconstruct the skill in subskills.
5. Obtain critical tools.
6. Eliminate barriers and distractions to practice.
7. Set up dedicated time for practice.
8. Create fast feedback loops.
9. Practice by the clock in short bursts.
10. Emphasize quantity and speed of practice.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;


    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Learning-Anything-Fast/&quot;&gt;Learning Anything Fast ʕ•̥͡•ʔ&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Van Phan  Josephine Kim at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Van and Josie&lt;/a&gt; on June 21, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organizing Me (ﾉ≧∀≦)ﾉ]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Organize-Me/" />
  <id>/Organize-Me</id>
  <updated>2015-06-02T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2015-06-02T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;٩(◜ᴗ◝ )۶&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned so much today but had no real time to really pause and reflect about it.&lt;br /&gt;
So it got me wondering.. This is really important to me, I should really do something about this new-found information. Now that we know these self-improving things or beneficial  knowledge, why does the next day feel the same?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So I think I’m on to something&lt;/em&gt;. We take little notes during our daily lives of things  that makes us go “Ah haa”. So at the end of the day I feel like it could go either way for  me.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I forget about it.  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It motivates and inspires me into productive work mode.  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even when #2 is on full throttle, eventually motivation wears off and you are then back to  square one. Both number 1 and 2 are not ways to better your life with this new knowledge  you have gained. These self-improvement notes don’t actually work unless&lt;br /&gt;
you &lt;em&gt;plan&lt;/em&gt;. We have to plan a way to start intergrating these new ideas into our lives.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I learned that it’s a good idea to keep track of your expenses and take 30%  of your income to invest in yourself. This was a very huge “ah haa” moment for me, but if  I were to go to bed now it would be the end of it because &lt;em&gt;I know my morning self has  things to do&lt;/em&gt;. So tonight I am going to make some sort of a to-do list. (You can implement  however you like, I just think lists are awesome) The things on this to-do list are there  to help me intergrate this new idea into my life.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please don’t ignore these great notes you have taken from articles, ted talks, or  grandpa Joe. &lt;em&gt;Become what you belive in, so that you can belive in what you have become&lt;/em&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Organize-Me/&quot;&gt;Organizing Me (ﾉ≧∀≦)ﾉ&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Van Phan  Josephine Kim at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Van and Josie&lt;/a&gt; on June 02, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investing Me ʕ·ᴥ· ʔ]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Investing-Me/" />
  <id>/Investing-Me</id>
  <updated>2015-05-27T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2015-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;ʕっ˘ڡ˘ςʔ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest I am so worried about how my post is structured that I wouldn’t even start&lt;br /&gt;
a sentence. Well fudge that, I’m done &lt;em&gt;obsessing&lt;/em&gt; over it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;starting-now&quot;&gt;STARTING NOW&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best advice that I cherish and live by is to invest in oneself. I swear people take &lt;br /&gt;
that to lightly. I see all these students perfecting their resume. This can relate to many  other things too and to a certain degree this is fine, but I draw the line when it is all that they invest in. Obsession can be a good indicator to see that the person is too   caught up with this external perfection that it takes away from their own value.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resumes are like trophies to show to people that you are awesome, this just happens to be  the norm within society. This makes sense but why do people decorate their trophies? Does  that make you even more awesome? I don’t think so.. So lets say a student spend all of&lt;br /&gt;
thier effort on font, font-size, styling, and down to the border of a resume layout.&lt;br /&gt;
That does not change your degree in lets say Bio-Chemistry. Sure it helps that it’s  readable and more pleasing to look at, but if you really want to show how amazing you&lt;br /&gt;
can be, you should use all of that time to go out there and get more trophies.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many useful skills and knowledge out there that desires your attention.&lt;br /&gt;
Invest yourself with books- the knowledge of many wise people to be downloaded into&lt;br /&gt;
your thoughts. Invest yourself with skills- with mastery you can create infinite amount of possibilities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;because-100-trophies-are-better-than-1-shiny-one&quot;&gt;Because 100 trophies are better than 1 shiny one.&lt;/h4&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Investing-Me/&quot;&gt;Investing Me ʕ·ᴥ· ʔ&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Van Phan  Josephine Kim at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Van and Josie&lt;/a&gt; on May 27, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where We Are ᶘ ᵒᴥᵒᶅ]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Born-Again/" />
  <id>/Born-Again</id>
  <updated>2015-05-22T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2015-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Van Phan  Josephine Kim</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>VanPhan514@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;ʕ￫ᴥ￩ʔ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month highlights a huge milestone for me: Graduation. Two years in a community college and the rest of the two years in a university have been a journey that I will never forget. The friends, professors, faculty, and advisors have impacted my life as an undergraduate student. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, the most important people who’ve supported my education since kindergarten are my mom and dad. They are the ones who’ve shown me that no matter how hard it gets, never give up and make my dreams a reality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m ready to embrace the new opportunities and connections I’ll encounter in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Born-Again/&quot;&gt;Where We Are ᶘ ᵒᴥᵒᶅ&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Van Phan  Josephine Kim at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Van and Josie&lt;/a&gt; on May 22, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>

</feed>
